https://www.mountvernon.org/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Last updated: October 4, 2018
The Mount Vernon Ladies Association of the Union ("us", "we", or "our") operates the https://www.mountvernon.org website (the "Service").
This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information when you use our Service.
We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.
We use your Personal Information for providing and improving the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible at https://www.mountvernon.org, and we ask that you please read these Terms and Conditions carefully before using our Service.
Information Collection And Use
While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to, your email address, name, phone number, postal address ("Personal Information").
Log Data
We collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Service ("Log Data"). This Log Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.
In addition, we may use third party services such as Google Analytics that collect, monitor and analyze this type of information in order to increase our Service's functionality. These third party service providers have their own privacy policies addressing how they use such information.
Cookies
Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer's hard drive.
We use cookies to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.
Service Providers
We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service, to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.
These third parties have access to your Personal Information only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.
Online Advertising
Our site uses third party tracking to allow us to display relevant ads to you based on your activity on our website. With this data, ad vendors can display ads that are likely to be of interest to you and control their frequency, preventing the same ad from being shown continuously. Tracking can also prevent ads from showing for products or services that you have already purchased. These third party vendors include but are not limited to Google AdWords, Facebook and AdRoll.
If you do not wish to participate in Google AdWords Remarketing, you can opt out by visiting Google's Ads Preferences Manager
You can also opt out of any third-party vendor's use of cookies by visiting www.networkadvertising.org/choices/
Email Communications
When you subscribe to our email newsletters, we will contact you with information that may be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving these communications by following the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any email we send, or you may email your request to newsletter@mountvernon.org.
Please note that we use a third party to send marketing emails, and your email address will be stored in that system.
Compliance With Laws
We will disclose your Personal Information where required to do so by law or subpoena or if we believe that such action is necessary to comply with the law and the reasonable requests of law enforcement or to protect the security or integrity of our Service.
Data Erasure Requests ("Right to be Forgotten")
We comply with data erasure requests, or the "right to be forgotten." If you have questions regarding our privacy policy or would like to have your personal data removed from our systems, please email privacy@mountvernon.org.
Security
The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
International Transfer
Your information, including Personal Information, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.
If you are located outside the United States and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the information, including Personal Information, to the United States and processes it there.
Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.
Links To Other Sites
Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.
We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.
Children's Privacy
Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 13 ("Children").
We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children have provided us with Personal Information, please contact us at privacy@mountvernon.org. If we discover that a child under 13 has provided us with Personal Information, we will delete such information from our servers immediately.
Changes To This Privacy Policy
We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.
You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.
Contact Us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please email us at privacy@mountvernon.org.
9 a.m. to 4 p.m.
iconDirections & Parking
buy tickets online & save
